Visit turkision.com for more!
Cerkutay, you should have gotten some rest first.
I can't heal if I don't work, my
Bey. Thank Allah I am fine.
I want all preparations to be done by tomorrow.
First, we will save Gunduz Bey.
Then if Allah permits,
Atranos will be our property.
If Allah permits, my Bey.
Let's take a look.
Victory lies in the craftmanship before battle.
It lies in the skill. Praise be, good work.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
Thanks.
What's the situation of the cart?
My Bey...
...we are following the instructions
drawn by Shahzade Alaeddin.
The masters are following them too.
Brothers, allow us.
In these veins...
...there will be gunpowder.
And we will destroy the infidels in Atranos.
And this cart will bring Imren's head to us.
But first, we will go to the frontier market.
We will take Olcaytu's gold and the ambassadors.
And from there, we will go to Imren
and take Gunduz Bey in exchange.
If Allah permits, my Bey.
Alps are ready for the battle.
Mehmet Bey will join us on the way.
Alright, alright.
Stop.
You are working, but you are still wounded.
My Bey, my heart is ready.
It wants ghaza. Please allow me.
And you told me that we would
try a smaller cart in the market.
You said that we would surprise
Imren Tegin as if he is a small bird.
I want to witness it.
We will surprise him, yeah.
Come on.
Imren ruined everything by trusting Osman.
This was going to be the base of Crusaders.
Now it's going to be our grave if Osman attacks us.
Don't be afraid, Cardinal. We are getting prepared.
Osman will die if he attacks us.
Imren gathered all his soldiers to the market.
Look, the Byzantine soldiers
with long spears are also here.
They strengthened the entrance.
There are long range archers on top of the gate.
We would be dead before we reach the gates.
It will be tough to take the frontier market, huh?
Wait.
We haven't made our last move yet.
Something's happening.
Imren keeps Olcaytu's gold here for security.
The ambassadors are still here too.
But they are getting ready to leave.
We need to be quick.
Come on.
I knew you wouldn't let that ignoble
Imren take frontier market my Bey.
May Allah bless you.
Praise be!
Where are you going?
I'm looking for Commander Husrev.
Not everyone who looks for him can find him.
What's your name?
Commander Husrev and I fought side by side.
He is good with double daggers.
His right arm is injured.
He got injured in a battle.
His eyes look sharp.
Yours aren't: like that though.
Konur!
How can you not recognize me?
If you don't remind me of yourself...
...how could I remember you, Konur?
You're right.
What is it?
From now on, I don't follow Osman Bey's orders.
I'll establish my own Beyhood.
I'll fight my own battle.
Okay brother.
Do it.
What do you want from us?
Hungry horse can't last long.
A lone soldier can't win.
You'll stand behind me from now on.
Like the old days.
Old days are gone, Konur.
Seljuk is no longer here.
We only scavenge for a living.
Go away.
Go and look for others.
I can tell.
You don't want Ghaza.
You only survive.
But you forget your real goal.
Now I'll tell you want you need.
And you'll like it.
Tell us what you want.
I'll give you gold.
Not a little bit.
They're Olcaytu Han's gold.
Ilkhanid's gold.
Mother.
We want to talk to you before father comes.
About the market?
It's not right to talk
about this during a battle...
...but waiting won't do us good.
Mother.
Me and Gonca made a decision.
We want to marry.
Gonca Hatun must be Kayi's daughter.
You know how this will end.
And Gonca..
...is engaged to Candaroglu.
Yes Bala Hatun.
We know what will happen.
It'll be hard...
..but we're adamant.
If you'll allow us, this is what we want.
When our duty is done I'll talk to father.
Will you support us mother?
Bala Hatun. Osman Bey and Mehmet Bey are coming.
Come on.
Peace be with you.
Peace be upon you.
What's the situation of the frontier market Bala?
Imren increased precautions.
But he can't be victorious against us.
So you say it's time.
Don't stand back Kanyumaz, listen well.
We're going to take the frontier market.
Tell them.
They reinforced the door, my bey.
They placed many obstacles at the entrance
of the frontier market and at the center of it.
Behind those obstacles, there are soldiers.
They strengthened the entrances
of the frontier market my bey.
They made them stronger with logs.
Soldiers constantly guard them.
You're telling me that
they're defending it like Turks.
But we're going to attack
them from their Byzantine side.
What do you have in mind Osman Bey?
What aren't you telling us?
We're going to attack them
with the thing they believe in.
Cerkutay.
My bey.
Let all the alps know.
As you wish my bey.
Now.
We're going to lay siege to...
...the frontier market from the front and the behind.
Bala Hatun.
Alaeddin, Gonca and the baciyans.
You're going to go in slowly from the behind.
When we attack from the
front, you're going to attack too.
As you wish my bey.
The Cardinal and the ambassadors.
When we attack them they'll start to run.
You have to be alert.
We're going to catch them quickly.
May our ghaza be mubarak.
Ameen.
Come on.
It's noon but we still are stuck here, my bey.
We have to be cautious.
If they see us they'll know that we
know where the hidden passages are.
But we won't wait for them
to get out of here either.
Oguz.
My bey.
Let Hasan know too.
As you wish my bey.
Elcim Hatun.
Don't be sad now.
We're going to get your father out of here.
I hope so.
My father was right in front of me...
...and I couldn't do anything.
If we made a move to save Gunduz Bey...
...that move wouldn't save him..
...but would get him killed.
But now...
Now we're the powerful ones.
We know where the hidden passages are.
The only think we have to do..
...is to make it out of here alive.
Elcim Hatun.
With Allah's permission we'll take both...
...Atranos and Gunduz Bey.
We will right?
We will.
My Shahzade.
What is it Hasan?
They found our horses.
How many are there?
25 for now.
They're in groups of 5.
We will cover our faces.
Even thought they see us,
they won't be sure about it.
If they recognize us then...
...we won't let any one of them live.
We don't have many people...
...but you still say that Orhan Bey.
They have more people...
...but we...
We are Turkish, Elcim Hatun.
Come on.
Oguz.
Boran and Konur.
It's going to cause Osman's
alps to fight each other.
If it doesn't, we will make it happen.
You did your part.
Now it's my turn.
You!
Traitor!
It was so easy to trick you.
You can only trick yourself.
Do your best!
Neither me, nor Osman Bey...
...will kneel before you!
I will die with my honor, but
I will never kneel before you!
Like your daughter-in-law Ayca?
You! What are you talking about?
You were so blind.
You couldn't see the truth.
But Ayca was different, she was smart.
What did you do to my daughter!?
To stop Kayis to unite and kill Elcim..
...I poisoned poor Ayca.
Holofira was a fool.
She sacrificed herself to save me.
But Ayca was smart.
Although the poison clouded her
mind, she knew I was behind everything.
When your treacherous
daughter-in-law came to me for alliance...
...I killed her.
You ignoble!
You will all end up like her.
Enjoy your time here for now.
I swear I am not going to die before I...
...kill you! May Allah be my witness!
You ignobles! You evil people!
You cruel people!
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER - FRONTIER MARKET
Who is that, Cardinal?
The papacy did not inform me of a squad coming.
Turks are coming!
Close the gates!
Turks are coming! Close the gates!
Hurry up! Close it!
The Righteous!
Attack!
Come on alps!
-Sisters! Attack!
-Allah is the Greatest!
Sisters, attack!
Alps, attack!
Baysungur, check the backside!
No one can go backside. If
you want, go check it yourself!
Come on!
Come here.
You think you can have my market?
You kicked me out.
But I'll never leave you my Bey.
I'll sacrifice myself for you.
I scattered all of you like dogs.
Another one. Come.
First I'll catch you.
Then I'll kill you.
Praise be, my brave brothers.
Great soldiers.
Are you slow? They're still standing.
Are you calling me old?
No. Praise be to you.
Good. I thought so.
Bala.
Wait.
You trust your swords too much.
Come.
Alps!
Kill everyone except the messengers.
Come on!
Long live Osman Bey!
Gonca.
Gonca, it's too late now.
I'll face anything.
Then don't stop until
it's done Alaeddin Bey.
I won't. I won't.
-Come on.
Come on.
We are victorious!
I wish I killed you before Osman.
Really? Messengers are
more important than you I guess.
You've lived for too long.
Come on then.
If you kill us the Pope will shred you...
Shut up.
Shut it.
You attacked our lands.
Do you think the land of the
Turks' don't have an owner?
And like that wasn't enough,
you think of attacking Jerusalem.
Envoy...
Come here.
Come here and tell me.
How many days does it take to come
here from the lands you were born in?
How many weeks? Tell me.
How many weeks does it take to
come here form your homelands?
You bring war to lands you
don't know at all, is that so?
You want to let the other Christians know...
...and start the
Crusades is that so?
So you want to start Crusades...
Look at me.
My name is Osman Bey.
I'm ending your Crusades...
...before they even started.
We're just doing what we're told.
We do...
...what the kings and the Pope tell us to do.
You have a saying.
No harm is to be done to an envoy.
You're not even an envoy.
You can only be the devil in a human body.
Envoys like you will get
hurt and they will be killed too.
There's someone there.
I heard something, let's go and check it out.
They must've heard it.
Drag these to aside.
Or hold on..
It's the land which you're not used to.
It must be hard to walk on it.
And conquering it, impossible.
Cerkutay.
My bey.
You'll go to Imren.
You will tell him that we have
the Cardinal and the envoys.
And he will give us Gunduz Bey in exchange of them.
Turahan.
You're going to take this with you as proof.
You'll do that so that they don't hurt Gunduz Bey.
As you wish my bey.
Now, Imren must be feeling good.
Let's go to him quickly to ruin it.
Tie these dogs to the horse.
As you command my Bey.
Get up!
Get up! Come on!
Come on!
Walk!
Well, Mehmet Bey.
We gave frontier market to the
infidels without your knowledge.
But thanks to the frontier market
we defeated many crusaders.
Raise the glorious sanjac of Germiyans.
The frontier market...
...belongs to Germiyan again.
I thought wrong of you all this time, Osman Bey.
Our anger and ambition clouded our eyes.
Thank you.
May your frontier market be prosperous.
I will inform my father about
what happened, Osman Bey.
Well, alps, bring the gold of Olcaytu.
We did what needed to be done,
and gave what was entrusted to us.
Now it's time to take them.
Come on.
Go on, Osman.
You don't know what's going to happen to you.
I pity you.
What happened here?
Turks! They attacked us.
They killed 3 of our soldiers.
You are not one of us!
Remove your helmets.
I thought you would bring me to a palace.
But you made me crawl on the ground.
But it worked.
Of course it worked.
It worked.
Elcim Hatun.
You look happier as you cut down infidels.
Come on, most of it is done.
We need to leave here.
Turks are there!
May Allah help us.
Allah is with us!
We will lure them to the forest.
There we will kill them all.
Send word to Atranos.
Orhan Bey, come on!
My shahzade!
That word won't reach Atranos!
No matter what!
What you did was dangerous.
I had to do it, Elcim Hatun.
I did what I needed to do.
Come on.
Our longing will be over now,
Gonca. I will talk to my father tonight.
And I will talk to my brother.
I'll send word to my father.
I don't care what happens.
No matter what they say...
...this tale will have a good ending.
We promised each other, student.
Come on.
Someone will see.
Come.
Look at these.
All the people who lose themselves for it...
...for this gold...
Alaeddin tell me.
My Bey.
Do you think Imren will only accept the messenger?
In return for Gunduz Bey..
...we'll give him the messengers and the cardinal.
If he's smart he'll accept it.
He's smart.
He's even smarter than we thought.
Gunduz Bey is important to us.
We value him. But...
...cardinal and the messengers...
...don't mean anything for Imren.
He's just a bug.
He keeps them for the Pope.
So I say...
...he'll want the gold too.
Then we will reveal..
...our wagon full of fire.
Right. Right. But...
...we won't give them gold.
We'll split the gold.
A part of it will go to the tribe.
The rest will go to secret
treasury under the lodge in Sogut.
Baysungur and Aykurt will take on this duty.
As you wish my Bey.
No one will know.
Bala.
Let's ask our daughter again.
She'll give us information on Atranos.
We must have leverage.
She'll do it for us.
We'll know everything about Atranos.
Alright.
Alps.
Everyone back to duty.
Let's go. Bala.
Carry the spears for the siege to the wagon.
When the army's at the Atranos gates...
...they'll use these spears okay?
As you wish Malhun Hatun.
Let's go.
Ulgen.
Malhun Hatun.
I can't find Ayse Hatun.
What do you mean?
Didn't the Alps see them?
No. We looked everywhere.
I'm thinking of something.
What if she followed Elcim Hatun?
Maybe she sent crazy again.
Don't think the worst Ulgen.
We'd know if that were the case.
Maybe she's taking a walk.
Send Alps to look for her.
Okay then.
Malhun Hatun.
What is it?
Send Osman Beymy regards.
Peace.be upon you.
It's important.
About Candaroglu.
Thank you.
This would ruin us all.
My Allah!
They'll track us down soon.
Hurry up.
If we leave they'll know we
know about the passages.
My father would be killed.
If we stay, we might not survive.
Our fathers rode to an unknown once, Elcim Hatun.
Right?
You seem softer ever since
your father was captured.
feel anxious Orhan Bey.
And...
...It's not just about my father.
Tell me Elcim Hatun.
What is it?
We don't have much time left until the wedding.
I don't want there to be any secrets between us.
The one who burned the dowry was Ayca.
Do you think they will be ready
until the wedding, Malhun Hatun?
We have lots to do.
Maybe we should postpone the wedding.
They will be done girl.
Why would Ayca Hatun do that?
Because of that poison.
My sister in law is getting
worse instead of better.
Holofira.
She died because of that poison too.
This might be happening because of her.
Elcim Hatun.
You just said that...
...there shouldn't be any secrets between us.
You're right.
My father played a game.
From the very start we knew that Olivia was guilty.
But to learn where the hidden
passages were at Atranos...
...we made it look like Holofira died...
...and played Olivia.
After we found out where the passages were...
...we were going to tell everyone the truth.
Thank Allah.
Aren't you mad that we...
...kept the truth from you?
On the contrary.
I'm happy that I didn't have the
blood of an innocent on my hands.
May Osman Bey live a long life.
He showed us how great he is once again.
It's alright, Elcim Hatun.
You're worthy to be the
bride to be to this beyhood with
your consciousness, fairness
and pure heart, Elcim Hatun.
Is Holofira okay?
She is.
...said our goodbyes to each other.
From now on..
...Holofira will walk her own path...
...and I will walk my own.
My Shahzade, they're coming.
Everyone to their positions, come on.
Come on.
Are you looking for me?
The one who is looking for her will find me or...
...their end.
Pull it.
Come on alps.
7, 8, 9...
One missing.
May Allah take mercy on the enemy, right?
Won't we hide them?
Before they find these bodies,
we will have already taken Atranos.
Come on.
Osman Bey is coming.
-My bey...
-Long live Osman Bey.
-Thank you Osman Bey.
-Osman Bey.
Congrats on your victory, father.
Thank you.
Thank you my beautiful daughter.
Welcome son.
Thank you mother.
Welcome my bey.
What is it?
My bey.
I have news but...
...it's bad.
Don't go, son.
You see, Gunduz Bey, you
sacrificed yourself for Osman Bey...
...but he sent his men to me out of fear.
And a dead man.
How are you still alive?
Well, Allah has not taken my life, Imren Tegin.
Maybe you are not powerful enough to kill me.
What does your weak Bey want from me?
You really don't know us.
Weakness is what suits you...
...not Osman Bey.
Speak before I cut off your tongue.
Or do you want to hang there
together with Gunduz Bey?
Turahan.
There won't be 3 people this time.
But we came not to talk, but to talk.
We are messengers. Control your anger.
Now, do you know why...
...I call you weak? Let me explain.
You worked together with crusaders and the pope.
But you couldn't defend the frontier market
You couldn't protect the ambassadors.
You couldn't protect the Cardinal.
So you are ashamed in front of the whole West...
...and everyone that worked with you were failed.
Then there is no need for Gunduz Bey to live.
Don't!
I am not finished yet.
Turahan.
Cardinal is alive.
Thank Allah.
Osman Bey made me proud even when I am a prisoner!
Do you think you will get away with this?
Taking the Cardinal as prisoner, huh?
You are confusing papacy
with the Tekfurs you fight!
Well, the pope and the
tekfurs are all the same for us.
An infidel is an infidel.
Now...
...shall we talk?
For whom do I fight?
They try to make treacherous
plans and hit us from behind.
While I am fighting in the front against the
Byzantine, they try to stab us in the back!
So this alliance was the
reason for Gonca to be married...
...to Candaroglu.
Germiyan and Candars are getting united.
They even set a goal ahead.
They are going to take Mekece
so I couldn't conquer Bursa.
First Mekece, and the forts around it.
That way, they will set a border
between me and Byzantine.
Their goal is to...
...stop me from conquering Bursa!
They want to stop my conquests.
But Yakup Bey looked as a
good man while he was leaving.
You were right to not give him your blessing.
If I killed them
I would be right.
Would I? Tell me.
But...
I won't let them stop me.
You talk of blood..
...but it's not just about alliance.
Gonca and Alaeddin are in love.
Their hearts belong together.
What heart are you talking of?
The homeland is at risk.
No.
What must be will be.
What must be...
Osman wants Gunduz Bey in return for cardinal?
That's right.
Let's talk with nice manners.
Let's do our business. But seeing him like this..
They'll make you pay for what you did.
But...
You kept yelling Imren.
What happened?
Did Osman Bey stop your breath?
Shut up!
-Enough!
Not enough!
You'll lose everything Imren.
Gunduz Bey;'s important to you right?
Not just cardinal.
I want the cardinal, messengers...
...and Olcaytu's gold.
But...
you don't..
...tell Osman, he an kill the cardinal.
And I...
..will send Gunduz Bey's head as a wedding gift.
Osman Bey;..
can't bargain with him...
...with this dog for me.
Don't make him make this dog happy.
If our enemy laughs...
...he must have lost half his teeth Gunduz Bey.
Don't worry.
...will tell my Bey.
And...
...he'll decide.
Now get out of here.
Allah Allah.
First the troops, then the crusaders base is gone.
Osman's coming to us.
What will we do now?
Cities can be conquered Olivia.
What matters is the cardinal
and the messengers to live.
Or all our allies will attack us.
Osman can't know.
He won't.
He'll give me what I want for Gunduz Bey.
He has to.
I'll get what I want...
...then I'll kill Osman.
Peace be with you.
Peace be upon you.
Thank Allah. I was scared that you're late.
Son. Are you okay?
We're okay mother. Thank Allah.
Good. Elcim?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Good.
Did you find out where the passages are?
We did. Thank Allah.
But Gunduz Bey...
...fell captive to Imren Tegin.
We know son.
My girl. Stay strong.
We know the passages.
We'll get your father out of there
safe and sound, if Allah permits.
I know Mother Malhun.
I can't stop it though.
Mother.
I'll let father know.
Be careful.
My girl.
I didn't want to say it now but...
...no one's seen Ayca in a while.
Is she lost?
We looked everywhere but we can't find her.
We thought she went with you.
Malhun Hatun.
While I was watching Olivia's tent at
night, Ayca Hatun was walking around it.
No we checked it.
Let's check again.
Come on then.
We finally succeeded right my Shahzade?
This cart will give us a lot Samil.
First, Gunduz Bey...
...and then the Atranos Castle.
And Imren's head.
Did you place the fire?
We did, my bey.
There's dust fire even in the wheels of the cart.
There will be a big explosion at Atranos.
It will be so big that...
...they'll hear it even from Constantinople.
Alaeddin.
Explain it to me.
Okay my bey.
We placed dust fire everywhere
in the skeleton of the cart.
Nothing can be seen on the outside.
The last chest will be place right here my bey.
Once this connects with the lit fuse...
...the infidels of Atranos will
resemble birds in the sky, my bey.
We said we'll make him sit at a branch like a bird.
He can't step on the floor.
They're going to fly.
But I don't want any mistakes
with this, just so you know.
Okay my bey.
My bey.
Son.
We figured out where the hidden
passages of Imren Tegin are, my bey.
Oh priase be!!
When sons fulfill their duties like this...
...victory becomes unavoidable as well.
Listen to me well.
Imren doesn't know that we know
about the hidden passages, so...
...we're going to take Gunduz
Bey after we give the envoys to him.
This cart which will be full
off gold will enter Atranos.
We will wait at the hidden
passages when that is happening.
Then..
...after this cart is inside the walls...
...there will be a big explosion.
Will it be during the day my bey?
Yes, if you take Kayi's Gunduz Bey's captive...
...then we will blow up your castle in the
middle of the day like this, right Samil?
In the middle of the day, yes.
When are confused by this...
...we will attack them.
Alright my Bey.
If Allah permits, my Bey.
We found the hidden
passages thanks to Holofira's act.
Of course, this had to remain hidden.
I understand it, I didn't take offense at all.
My great bride, thank you.
But you know this right?
Even though Olivia left,
this is still a secret. Ayca...
I will never tell her.
I can't trust her while she's like this anyways.
Mother Malhun.
Ayca is the one who started the fire.
What are you saying Elcim?
But it's all because of that poison.
She lost her mind, if it wasn't
for that she wouldn't have done it.
I fear she might do something to herself now.
We're going to find her, don't worry.
Then we will be more careful for her safety.
Come on.
Ayca...
She wanted to kill Olivia the moment she saw her.
Hold on don't worry.
We're going to find her.
I have a very bad feeling.
Allah Allah...
What's that?
No...
Elcim, girl...
She killed her...
She killed my sister in law...
She was left to us by my brother!
-Orhan.
-Mother.
What is going on?
I swear I am going to kill Olivia with my hands.
We will take her revenge.
I am going to kill her.
We will take the gold here.
When they pass through here,
we will take it somewhere safe.
Look at you.
Now you are gathering men against my men!?
You couldn't be exiled honorably?
Boran.
We fought, we paid the price, and it's over.
They are all honorable*^
soldiers from Seljuk state.
Know your place.
Go away.
You gather them around...
...and stand against my Bey?
I will not allow that!
Are you going to do that alone?
You speak like an enemy.
So you will be my enemy.
You won't listen to reason.
Well, then you deserve a beating.
Go on, brave ones!
Come on
Give it to me.
What did he use to trick you?
No one is tricked, we are
all following our own paths.
But your path leads to death.
I will die on the righteous path. lam sure of it.
Come on!
Priest sends is regards Jesus' soldiers.
We're here to take the swords of church.
This is it. Hurry, the units are coming.
How did you know the church would receive swords?
My aunt won't start a war
without the support of the church.
These are Bursa Tekfur's soldiers.
Ayca was a good girl.
Olivia poisoned her...
...then she died when she went crazy.
Don't worry mother.
They won't get away with it.
Of course.
Did you see Elcim after Ayca's funeral?
Son.
You'll marry Elcim eventually.
She needs you at a time like this. See her.
Mother.
Elcim Hatun's strong.
She'll get through it.
Of course she will. She's strong.
But her father's captive.
Her aunt in law died.
She has no one but you.
Be with her.
Okay.
I'll go see her now.
Stop. Who are you?
Bala Hatun expects us.
Pass.
Son.
My Bey.
What are you doing?
The wagon's ready my Bey.
The system is functional.
Everything's ready, thank Allah.
Alright, alright.
Imren can think about the rest.
Right. Right.
Yagiz Alp. Put on the lid.
Father.
If you have time I wish to talk.
Tell me. What is it?
Father.
I want to marry Gonca Hatun.
Gonca Hatun is a woman
worthy of our tribe and family.
I vouch for her.
Gonca is a good girl.
But...
...she's engaged son.
Can you fight that?
Can you?
Can you brave this hard task Alaeddin Ali?
I know my Bey.
But I thought about it.
I'm willing to fight this battle for love.
Germiyanids won't allow this marriage.
What about Gonca?
Can she...
...stand against her family?
Gonca wants this my Bey.
We set out together.
Look son.
Your brother Orhan.
For the future of our beyhood..
..he gave up on his love.
And now you...
...for the future of our beyhood...
You're going to marry Gonca.
Allah.
That's all Bala Hatun.
Imren Tegin got support from Bursa.
They're going to wait in case of
a possible attack inside the castle.
So that it huh?
Okay.
Thanks to you we know everything
about the trap they tried to set.
You helped us so much...
Thank you.
You reminded me of the
kindness of my mother
whose voice I can't even
remember now, Bala Hatun.
It's not even enough.
I want your victory more than anything.
Not just for myself either.
I want it for all the oppressed people.
I want people like Olivia and Imren Tegin not to...
...die before they experience
what they made others experience.
Don't worry girl.
Those cruel people will get their
share from Osman Bey's justice.
Until then you'll stay at the tribe, with us.
For your safety.
Okay then.
Can I come in Elcim Hatun?
Come in Orhan Bey.
Elcim Hatun.
I know you want to be alone...
...but I'm worried about you.
Thank you.
But I can't stop thinking about my aunt.
We went through so much together...
You're a very strong woman.
I know that but you shouldn't
hide your pain from me.
We're one now.
Cry Elcim Hatun.
Cry, it will help.
I don't want to
believe it Orhan Bey.
My father is captive at the hands of the enemy.
My sister in law was murdered...
What kind of a test is this?
I'm not complaining, may Allah forgive.
But I will kill Olivia with my bare hands.
From now on, your pain is my pain.
Your revenge is my revenge.
But just know this. The
revenge you're wishing for...
...is not that far away.
We figured out where the
hidden passages are at Atranos.
Now, we have the upper hand right?
Thank Allah.
But I know that, if I have the
hope to reunite with my father now...
...it's all thanks to Holofira acting dead.
If not we couldn't have find the passages.
I owe her an apology.
Holofira has a big heart, Elcim Hatun.
She must've understood your reasoning on her own.
But don't think about these things now.
Rest well.
Tomorrow will be a hard day.
Excuse me.
May Allah protect you, Elcim Hatun.
Once the sun raises we will take both
Atranos and Gunduz Bey, if Allah permits.
If Allah permits.
Who is there?
Holofira.
I brought information about Atranos.
Bala Hatun asked me to
stay here until the conquest.
-I couldn't disobey her.
-Okay.
You did well.
Mother Bala thought well.
But I don't want to bother anyone.
I won't come out of my tent either.
Elcim Hatun, you must have heard...
...Imren Tegin imprisoned Gunduz Bey.
And her sister Ayca passed away.
She is devastated.
That's why, I...
You will get married soon.
You should be with her.
I am so sorry about it.
Bala Hatun told me everything.
I hope my aunt will get her punishment.
What about you?
How are you, Holofira?
Your tent is ready, Holofira Hatun.
I am as how you
left me, Orhan Bey.
I am fine.
And I will get better.
Now, excuse me.
I don't understand, father. What
does this mean? Did I hear you right?
Yeah, you heard me right.
Father.
-You heard me right.
-Father!
Alaeddin Ali.
Look...
...I knew there was something wrong
with this marriage since the beginning.
And I was right. Mehmet Bey...
...his attitude in the divan.
It was obvious.
You see, son, it's not always
the infidels that cause fitna.
Our brothers started causing it too.
What's with their treachery, my Bey?
Germiyan and Candaroglu.
They want to stop us by making an alliance.
To stop the conquest of Bursa and Iznik...
...they set Mekece as their goals.
And they even sent a messenger
to the commander of the castle.
What's their goal, my Bey?
More than just conquest?
Mekece has nothing to do with
conquest. It's not even in their path.
Then you are telling me that they
want to settle in Byzantine borders...
...and stop us from advancing, huh?
We will understand what they want.
And we will make our move accordingly.
How are we going to know that, my Bey?
Well, they are
Now, they will come to the wedding of...
...the son of great Osman Bey, Orhan Bey.
They will want to look good.
There we will understand their intentions.
But, the marriage they want won't happen.
Never.
As you command, my Bey.
Now...
...you are thinking that if this
wasn't a political marriage...
...then...
...if I would support you like this or not.
Right?
Look son.
I talk to you...
...and I didn't tell you,
you can't marry her.
I support you.
I will help you.
You'll marry Gonca.
I'm glad you're here father.
I'm glad you're here.
My brave boy. My brave boy.
My Bey.
Sorry to interrupt.
Imren Tegin...
In return for Gunduz Bey...
...he wants the gold too.
Well...
Of course he does.
We'll give him more than that.
Thank you father.
Germiyanoglu Border - Frontier Market
Tell me Gonca.
What do you want to talk about?
I won't marry Candaroglu.
What are you saying Gonca?
The promise was made.
I didn't promise anyone brother.
I'll send word to my father.
Gonca.
I'll marry Alaeddin who I love and loves me.
You lost your mind.
I haven't.
I won't let anyone hurt me.
This is my last word brother.
You'll marry Alaeddin?
My father won't allow it.
I'll talk to him and he'll allow it.
But...
...if he doesn't...
If he doesn't?
What will you do?
Run off with Alaeddin?
Will you?
I won't let you.
Guice.
Fitnat. Cage Gonca in the tent.
Don't.
Brother.
Let go. Let me go brother.
You can't do this to me okay?
Is this how you'll stop me?
You can't stop me.
If I don't lock you, you'll slander our name.
I won't let it.
Brother.
Alps will stay by the tent.
Let go.
-Come on.
Is this how you'll stop me?
Let me go.
-Brother.
Stop!
How dare you stop us?
Give us the gold.
And we'll let you go.
Alps never bend to scavengers. We won't do it now.
Alps!
You can't have the gold before killing us.
Then it's a shame.
Don't fight.
We'll kill you all.
Konur Bey.
You work with scavengers?
Shame on you.
Shut up.
Don't do this Konur Bey.
This is my Beys gold.
You'll be in trouble.
It's mine now.
Take the gold.
Come on.
To save the Alps...
...we'll give you the gold.
But...
...when Osman Bey hears this...
...he'll go after you.
It's okay.
Take the horses...
...so they don't follow us.
Konur Bey.
What happened Aykurt?
Did the one you trust betray it?
Let's see what's going to happen
once Osman Bey hears this.
Shame.
Come on, alps, come on.
The brave men of Kayi...
...sisters...
We...
...chose Kestle, Kite and Atranos...
...for Bursa...
...as targets.
But now the infidels only have Atranos now.
They wanted to use Atranos as a headquarter.
They wanted to gather their armies there...
...and then attack our lands.
However, thank Allah, we didn't let them.
Thank Allah!
Now...
...this is the last day of
the infidels having Atranos.
First, we will conquer it.
We're going to save Gunduz Bey.
And then we will parade that Imren's
head from one land to the other.
They will see what the end of those
who want to attack our lands meet.
Now tell me.
The brave men of Kayi...
...honorable sisters...
...are you with me to fight...
...on this mubarak Ramadan day?
We are Osman Bey.
Are you with me?
Thank you, thank you.
Now we're going-to save Gunduz Bey.
Then swords and..
...fire will do the talking.
Come on.
Germitanoglu Border - Frontier Market
I don't want any mistakes.
This market will be better
than it was before. Come on.
As you wish my Shahzade.
Someone trusted to you is
a very big challenge right?
Mehmet Bey.
Our Prophet said...
...if you have something that was
trusted to you then wait for the doomsday.
You say it so well Dervish.
Right.
It's a big challenge.
But thank Allah...
...I don't betray it.
This market will be better than it
was when Yakup Bey left it to me.
We don't know if it's your
nafs or your heart that's talking.
But did Yakup Bey trust you with just this market?
Then again the other one...
...was trusted to you way before this.
In The Farewell Sermon...
In Thet Farewell Sermon...
...the Prophet says, women
are trusted to you by Allah.
If you don't take care of it...
...if you don't offer them peace...
...then you bring your life closer to doomsday.
I have my mother and sister.
I take care of them both.
My sister...
For her happiness...
...I even risk being the bad guy in her eyes.
So, you make decisions for her, is that so?
I just thought of this.
One day, a woman...
...goes to our Prophet...
"Oh prophet, my father is making me marry...
...to his brother's son, to gain more reputation."
"But I don't want it."
The prophet called her father.
And did not accept father's decision
without the consent of the daughter.
He let the girl decide whether
or not she wants to marry.
Now you might ask why I am telling you all these.
So you can find the path of Haqq through sunnah.
So you can act with your heart, not with your nafs.
So you can be sure you do not
betray what's entrusted to you.
Prophet says...
"Only those with dignity...
...and honor value the women".
"Only evil and degenerate ones see them lowly"
May Allah make you and everyone...
...become one of those with dignity and honor.
Ameen, Dervish afendi.
Stay safe.
Gonca.
Sister.
Gunduz Bey is here, Osman Bey.
He is not as healthy as when I captured him.
And I got Cardinal and the ambassadors.
Bring them.
Come here.
You dared to hit them, huh?
Imren Tegin or whatever your name is.
I am going to torment you more!
But you did not even do anything remarkable.
You just hide in holes like a rat.
You devise treacherous schemes.
And that's what suits you best.
You will soon see my power.
I will turn you
mad out of anger.
And I will be there to take
your head in your first mistake.
Yeah, yeah.
The war is just beginning.
No. the war will be over soon.
Now give Gunduz Bey to me.
Osman Bey.
Olivia, I am taking my father back...
...but I will make you pay
for my sister-in-law Ayca!
I am going to take your pitiful life with my hands!
You will end up like your crazy sister too.
You should pray to Cardinal
for your father's safety.
Gunduz Bey, are you okay?
I am okay, Osman Bey, thank you.
Okay.
Father.
I am okay, my girl.
Thanks to Osman Bey.
Father, Ayca...
I heard about it in my imprisonment.
I am sorry for our loss.
It would be better if we hadn't
sent these dogs, Osman Bey.
Don't worry, Gunduz Bey.
We will take their lives, and their castles.
Our trade ends here, Osman Bey.
Don't forget, until one of us dies.
Until one of us dies.
But you should not forget this either.
You don't have much time left.
What are we going to do now, huh Osman Bey?
We came here to take Atranos.
And we will do that.
We are going to Atranos, come on alps!
Long live Imren Tegin!
Prepare festivities for taking the
gold back and saving the cardinal.
Today is our day.
Our day?
Because of you stupidity we almost died.
You trusted Osman and ruined it all.
You'll pay for it.
Imren Tegin.
No.
Nothing over yet.
When the crusaders come...
There are no crusaders.
I'll revoke your authority.
I brought together the Pope and Olcaytu.
No one can revoke anything.
You trust yourself too much.
Your failure will be known and you'll die.
This is a war.
And war is not over.
But you're cowards.
I can't win with cowards.
You can't talk to us like that.
You're right.
No more talking.
Bend the knee.
If you kill me Pope will destroy you.
Don't worry cardinal.
I won't kill you.
You'll tell Pope what I'll say.
Ayca.
My daughter in law.
My son left her to me.
I couldn't protect my son...
...or his wife.
Don't blame yourself father.
She lost her mind.
We couldn't protect her mind.
We couldn't stop the poison.
We're responsible for
When I kill Olivia, she'll be avenged.
I never knew...
...he'd go this far.
He did it.
-He did it.
Cerkutay Bey.
The Konur I saw...
...wasn't the one I know.
He's right.
We knew him wrong.
Don't say that Baysungur.
He's Konur Bey.
Nothing can excuse him trapping Alps...
...and taking Osman Bey's gold.
Don't do this brothers.
Alps.
What are you talking about?
My Bey.
I don't want to say it but...
...Konur Bey...
...took the gold we sent to Sogut.
He had some disordered men with him.
Konur's on his own.
There's nothing to say.
I wish he won't die by my hand.
Come on. Give the Alps the news.
Atranos...
...will be Turk's today.
-If Allah permits, my Bey.
Come on.
Long Live Imren Tegin!
My Bey.
We can't go further with horses.
Let's go.
Alps.
We'll move quietly.
We have a castle to conquer...
...and a head to cut off.
Come on.
We'll go to Osman Bey.
Sisters.
Watch our backs.
Come on
This way my bey.
This is the hidden passage, my bey.
Atranos will become Turks' land today.
Imren.
Your time is up now.
You'll die today.
Alps.
Come on.
Allah is Everlasting.
We have to pass these
passages before that cart explodes.
Be careful.
We won't let anyone go out of here.
I won't any one of them live.
I won't stop until I take my
daughter's revenge, Osman Bey.
Gunduz Bey who has hold
on to his revenge, don't worry.
Today is the day of revenge.
If Allah permits, if Allah permits.
Come on.
Sisters, we're going to stay here.
We will hunt down cowards that leave the castle.
Come on.
Your people are proud of you.
Long live Imren Tegin.
Imren Tegin.
Loyal subjects of Rome.
The strong soldiers of blessed lands.
This gold signals our rebirth...
...and Osman's death.
Death to Osman.
Osman who has subjected Rome to fear...
...will die now.
That coward's land will be
destroyed under our horses' shoes.
His men will die by our soldier's swords.
These lands which they've turned into
hell will become heaven with us again.
Under the shadow of my
nation everyone will find peace.
Long live Imren Tegin.
Long live Imren Tegin!
Take the gold to the vault.
We don't have much time, come on.
Olivia.
Tell me about the tribes
Osman have in the plateaus.
How many people there are,
where are they? I want all the details.
I will be grateful to you if you
destroy that goat-smelling tribe.
Don't worry, I will make Osman experience hell.
The infidels must have
felt that explosion. Come on.
Osman!
It's time to make Atranos the property of Turks.
Come on!
Come on
Come here! Come Imren Tegin!
All of you, come!
Imren Tegin!
Allah has given me the permission,
and the opportunity. Today is the last day.
Alps!
Attack!
Olivia!
No one will escape Osman Bey's justice today.
Haqq
Now attack!
Come on. To the passages.
Osman!
I won't be defeated by you today.
Today Atranos will be your grave.
Orhan! Alaeddin!
To the gates!
As you wish my Bey.
What will we do?
We'll never give up! Never!
Don't run Olivia.
You'll pay for what you did.
Allah!
Support the gates!
The gates or the walls...
...can't save you from me.
Allah is the Greatest!
Come on!
Those who attack Turk's lands...
...will die for it.
Allah is the Greatest!
You'll pay for this Osman!
Don't run Imren!
You'll only die tired.
Olivia.
Kill them all.
Destroy them
Don't let them pass.
Kill them all.
Attack!
Kill them all. I'm going to find that snake.
Imren!
We used to say one of us..
Guess this is the day.
I told you you didn't have much time left.
We'll see.
Come then.
Andra.
Go and get help.
Okay.
Come on then Elcim. Come.
Your death will be very painful Elcim.
When this poison gets mixed in your bloodstream...
...you won't be able to escape.
Where will you run this time then?
This is the end of the road Olivia.
Come out.
I know you're here.
You killed Ayca without mercy.
I swear, I won't take mercy on you either.
Ayca had an easy death.
But yours won't be easy at all.
You're going to die a painful death.
So you poisoned your swords...
You won't be able to run this time.
You paved the way to hell yourself.
May your suffering be hard.
Did you really think I was
going to run away from you?
Do you know why they call
me the Rome's executioner?
You'll learn now.
Don't worry, after I kill you...
...I will be called the
executioner of executioners!
Then, until one of us dies.
Until one of us dies.
Come here.
Is this all you got, Osman?
You attacked my lands!
You are a disgrace-of the lineage!
You brought shame to the lineage!
Even the soil will reject you!
Imren Tegin or whatever your name is!
You got what you deserved.
Take him.
Get up!
Thank Allah, Atranos is the property of Turks now.
Thank Allah.
Are you okay?
We are okay, thank Allah.
-Father.
-Elcim.
My girl.
I took Ayca's revenge, I killed Olivia.
Live long, my girl!
Where is Osman Bey?
My Bey is coming.
Thank Allah.
Come on alps.
Bring the pillar here.
It's time for justice.
Imren Tegin!
Osman Bey took Atranos castle.
So that's how Imren Tegin dies.
Husrev, split half of the gold among yourselves.
The other half is my sword right.
What are you going to do with all that gold, Konur?
The war is just beginning.
We need soldiers and weapons.
We will go for Mekece castle.
We will continue our cause there.
Cardinal.
Come here.
Alps.
Sit him down.
You think you could get away from me?
You think I'd let infidels take these lands?
Where is he?
Hm?
Where's the man you trusted?
Here...
Here he is.
Now...
...you wanted to be the new pope.
If you were victorious...
..maybe you'd be the pope.
But now...
...you'll return...
...with defeat...
...and with the head of Imren.
They wanted to stop us.
But we won't stop.
Our goal is clear.
Bursa on one side...
...and Nicaea on the other.
Not just one day.
It will be now.
Gunduz Bey.
You'll head out with ALps.
You'll lay siege on Nicaea.
And I will...
..go to Bursa.
You're insane Osman Bey.
These are dreams...
Byzantine still lives.
Bursa and Nicaea...
...will be ours...
...sooner or later.
Cardinal.
Everything that's yours...
...will be ours.
Take him to his horse.
Send him to the pope.
You'll tell the pope...
...what happened in this land...
...and Osman Bey.
Come on.
We'll come back stronger Osman Bey.
When you come back...
...you'll find a Great Empire.
Come on.
We...
...will go to Bursa and Nicaea.
And Cerkutay...
-My Bey.
You will go to Mekece as a messenger.
And tell them...
...'two cities...
...are under siege.
You will not receive any help.
...give us Mekece in peace.'
As you wish my Bey.
Alright.
Take this dog down.
War is over Osman.
This war...
...will end now.
This end will be your death...
...and will be our wedding.
You tried to stop this
wedding with all those tricks.
There. My daughter Elcim Hatun.
My son, Orhan.
With Allah's permission, we're
going to hold their wedding feast.
I want you to...
..know this before you die.
May them be happy all their lives, Osman Bey.
What can I say?
Finally you united two Turk beyhoods.
Shut it.
Don't mention Turks' name every again. Get up.
Don't mention Turk's name every again.
You don't have loyalty in your blood, just poverty.
You're a man who has stabbed
your own kind in the back.
You are a shame to your bloodline...
...and the black sheep of Seljuks.
Akca's dog...
What other name of yours should I curse?
You've wasted yourself for a cause.
If you didn't have a cause you would be nothing.
You'll die all alone.
Customs, ghaza...AII of them are lies.
Is that so?
Look.
This axe I'm holding...
..is the truth itself.
But I...
...will never give up on our customs.
You...
...are from the bloodline of the dynasty.
Damn it.
To hell to my bloodline...
...to your custom...
...to your ghaza.
All of you will burn in hell fire.
All of you.
The war..
...is over now.
Take him away.
Send him to the Emperor.
Tell him...
...that if another commander comes into my lands...
...then I won't kill him but
come and kill him in his palace.
With the bravery of the sons...
...the bravery of the men...
...and...
...with the talents of the baciyans...
...victory is ours once again.
We succeeded huh Osman Bey?
We did.
Thank Allah.
Cerkutay.
Are you tired Cerkutay?
My bey...
Don't.
We're just getting started.
There are more castles to
conquer and more infidels to destroy.
Thank Allah who holds us responsible...
...not with victory but with conquests...
-Allah is the Greatest!
-Allah is the Greatest
Allah is the Greatest!
Visit turkision.com for more!